## Joshua Petersen

Email: joshuavpetersen01@gmail.com

Mobile: 07496212390

Portfolio: jvp2001.github.io

### **Profile**

Undergraduate programmer currently studying Computer Games Programming at the University of Gloucestershire, whose goal is to work as a programmer in the games industry.

I have had to learn to improve my organisation and communication skills during my academic life.

I have worked hard throughout all areas of my life to enhance these skills as well as learn to be flexible and adaptable. At university, I have particularly enjoyed learning more about Unreal Engine.

# **Key Skills**

- Demonstrated teamwork and problem solving during two years of volunteering work and working on Level 6 Golem project
- Windows, MacOS, Linux environments.
- C++, as demonstrated by my Unreal UI mock up and in assignment
- Java, C# and Python
- The Unreal Engine and JetBrains' IDE

#### **Education**

### 2020- Present

**BSC (Hons) Computer Games Programming,** University of Gloucestershire

## A-Levels 2019 - 2021

CompTIA A+ 900 series	Pass
Level 3 BTEC Extended Certificate Applied Science	Merit

Advanced Cyberfirst Course August 2018

Cisco CCNA Level 3: Unit 1: Introduction to Networks

Cisco CCNA Level 3: Unit 2: Routing & Switching Essentials

Cisco CCNA Level 3: Unit 3: Scaling Networks

Pass

Cisco CCNA Industry Certification

Pass

OCR A/S Computer Science

В

Cisco IT Essentials (Level 2)

**Pass** 

## **GCSEs 2019**

Computer Science (A), Mathematics, English Language (5), Physics, Chemistry, Biology (B), Geography (C), English Functional Skills Level 2 (Pass)

## **Work Experience**

**2018 – 2020** Classroom Assistant: Year 7 & 8 ICT, Year 10 Cisco IT Essentials

I helped years 7 to 10 with ICT, by answering their questions and helping individuals with their practical work

**2018 - 2020** Volunteer with IT Schools Africa, Cheltenham

In my sixth form years, I volunteered for a charity based in Cheltenham called IT schools for Africa. The charity took second hand IT equipment, revamped them, installed up-to-date software, and shipped them to African Schools, mainly in Mali.

Present Informal support of undergraduate engineering student with programming Arduino (C++).

## Interests

- Achieved Bronze, Duke of Edinburgh Awards
- Cryptology
- Rock Climbing: NICAS Level 2
- Games: particularly board and card games

### References

Available on request